Kirsty Goodary

Junior Full Stack Developer

- kirstygoodary1@gmail.com
- **** 07368640599
- kirstygoodary.github.io/Portfolio/

Technical Took kit

Front End: (Front End: Node.js, React.js, Axios, HTML, CSS, good understanding of React Native.), Back End (Express, Postgres, SQL, Knex, Node.js, good understanding of Firebase and AWS.), Testing (Mocha, Chai, Jest, Sinon)

Technologies I am interested in

Linux (I currently use the MacOS operating system. I am interested in Linux because it operates on a wider range of hardware.),

Python (I am interested in learning how Python supports Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning.)

Interests

Member of Code and Stuff - in addition to attending Northcoders programme, I attend a weekly meetup for women and non-binary people. Their mission is to bring more women and non-binary people into the industry through mentoring. I enjoy meeting other enthusiasts and I'm keen to learn other technologies after completing the course. I am supportive of their mission and aim to become a mentor in the future.

Attending High Intensity Interval Training sessions after work.

Socialising with friends and colleagues.

Awards

Club Colours Award

I was awarded the Club Colours award at university for managing a sports club, whilst studying and working full time.

Legaltech Hackathon

I won the Legaltech Hackathon 2020, hosted by Barclays Eagle Labs and Office and Dragons. The product is now in the process of development support from Barclays Eagle Labs and the Law Society.

Summary

After working in the legal industry for 8 years, I am looking for a new challenge and I have been training to be a junior full stack developer at Northcoders.

I am very hardworking and results driven. I take pride in exceeding my objectives. In my previous roles, I consistently exceeded my targets. These roles also required me to follow fast paced processes, meet deadlines and problem solve. I work very well in a team, I also work equally as well on my own.

I also am a member of Code and Stuff, a meetup group for women and non-binary persons.

Professional Experience

Pillar Project, Junior Backend Developer (internship)

03/2020 - present

 Developing a content aggregation API for Pillar's social media, which can be used on other platforms

Pillar Project, Junior Backend Developer

03/2020 - present

- Assisting the Tech Lead.
- Developing a content aggregation API for social media.

Northcoders, Trainee Full Stack Developer

11/2019 - 02/2020

A full stack coding bootcamp which teaches an industry-led curriculum. Throughout the course, I completed TDD, utilised version control and pair programming.

The final 3 weeks involve working in a team of 4, practicing daily stand ups, and using a Kanban board before we present our project at the end.

Keoghs LLP, Litigation Executive

05/2016 - 11/2019

- Handling a caseload of approximately 100 litigated claims. Working to tight deadlines.
- Consistently exceeding monthly targets.

JB Leitch LLP, Litigation Assistant

09/2011 - 09/2013

- Assisting Fee Earners with their caseload.
- Volunteered to be and acted as Fire Warden.

Horwich Farrelly, Litigation Executive

09/2011 - 05/2013

- Handling a caseload of approximately 150 litigated claims. Working in a high pressure environment.
- Consistently exceeding targets and objectives.

Education

CILEx Law School, Diploma in Legal Practice

2014 - 2015

Distinction

CILEx Law School, Diploma in Legal Practice

2014 - 2015

Distinction

Liverpool John Moores University, Law LLB

2006 - 2009

2:1

Legaltech Hackathon

I won the Legaltech hackathon in March 2020, hosted by Barclays Eagle Labs and Office & Dragons. The product idea is now in development with the support from Barclays Eagle Labs and the Law Society.

Rainford College, A Level

2004 – 2006

B in English Language, English Literature and Psychology